<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Optical Emotions</string>

    <string name="unbreakable_summary">I am confident in my capabilities to handle any task through dedication, vigilance, and
maintaining a sense of control. Despite the urge to accomplish everything, I acknowledge the
importance of persistence in bringing about improvement. I take pride in being seen as
dependable and strong, always ready to face any challenge without showing vulnerability.
However, I recognize that my excessive focus on practical matters often leads me to overlook
my aspirations, and I tend to make excuses to maintain the safety and predictability of my
life. Nevertheless, the satisfaction I derive from being perceived as dependable and prepared
remains significant to me</string>
    <string name="inspector_summary">In my relentless pursuit of excellence, I hold the firm belief that anything less than
perfection is unacceptable. I dedicate myself to achieving flawlessness in every aspect of my
life, which breeds guilt, shame, self-doubt, and a fear of failure when I make even the slightest
mistake or fall short of my high expectations. This constant comparison to others while
measuring my circumstances against an idealized scenario fuels feelings of inadequacy, envy,
and jealousy toward those who have achieved success. This behavior serves to intensify my
sense of inferiority and dissatisfaction with my own abilities.</string>
    <string name="savior_summary">Taking responsibility for the problems of others makes me feel valuable and distinctive. I
believe that if I don\'t help others, it implies that I don\'t care for or love them. I hold myself
accountable for the pain that my loved ones experience. I believe that caring excessively for
others increases my own self-worth.</string>
    <string name="rejected_summary">I erect emotional walls that prevent others from getting too close to me, hoping that this
will shield me from getting hurt. My self-esteem is linked to receiving approval from others,
and I forget that self- acceptance should come first. I hold onto relationships that are harmful
to my overall health and leave me feeling drained. I struggle with emotional closeness and
avoid showing vulnerability, which makes me value my independence even more.</string>
    <string name="pessimist_summary">I focus on the most unfavorable possible outcomes of every situation. I give most of my
attention to the potential risks and negative aspects, while overlooking the possible benefits.
I believe that every good thing has an expiration date. I engage in negative self-talk and tend
to dismiss positive assumptions</string>
    <string name="doer_summary">I frequently push myself beyond my physical limits, taking on tasks that exceed my capabilities, and viewing rest as a waste of time, which hinders my growth and progress. My conviction that my value is tied to my productivity leads me to believe that the most respected people are the ones who work tirelessly. I postpone my happiness, believing it will only come with the attainment of specific objectives and prosperity. My self-worth is linked to external accomplishments and the recognition they bring, causing me to push myself to exhaustion in pursuit of success. Yet, when I am unable to meet my lofty expectations, I succumb to harsh self-criticism, trapped in the paradox of relentless achievement. If someone asked me to describe my life, I would say it is a conundrum of relentless achievement.</string>
    <string name="conformer_summary">I struggle to set healthy boundaries, often prioritizing the needs of others over my own,
and find validation in accommodating them, even at the expense of my well-being. I seek
recognition through noble suffering and unwavering sacrifice, while downplaying material
possessions. I frequently engage in conversations revolving around crises, and perceive
challenges as overwhelming, often feeling powerless and burdened by past traumas</string>
    <string name="dreamer_summary">In order to avoid confronting my emotions, I turn to immediate gratification, such as
overeating, drinking, spending money, and binge-watching TV. These behaviors are not
beneficial to me in the long run, but they help to distract me from my reality. I have a tendency
to think that if I feel sad, there must be something wrong with me. I hold onto the belief that
it is not appropriate to share my negative emotions with others.</string>
    <string name="summary_title">"Summary "</string>
    <string name="exercises">Exercises</string>
    <string name="unbreakable_exercises">The Mindful Bus Ride\nDelegating With Confidence\nExpress Coherently, Aligning Your Heart &amp; Brain\nLeveraging The Relationships Capital\nPerspective Taking: Understanding Others\nPromote Spontaneity and Openness\nStrengthen Your Flexibility Muscle</string>
    <string name="inspector_exercises">The Mindful Bus Ride\nHardliner Perfectionist\nLeveraging The Relationships Capital\nOvercome The Fear Of Failure\nStrengthenYour Flexibility Muscle\nTaking Pride In Your Achievements\nWhere Talent Meets Opportunity</string>
    <string name="savior_exercises">The Mindful Bus Ride\nBenefits Of Achieving Self-Actualization\nLearn To Speak Assertively\nLet Actions-Not Impressions-Prevail\nStop Over-Identification\nWhy Self-Care Isn\'t Selfish</string>
    <string name="rejected_exercises">The Mindful Bus Ride\nCracking The Rejection Code\nEnd Indecisiveness And Neediness\nLet Actions-Not Impressions-Prevail\nThe Real Consequence of Problem-Solving\nThings Are Not Happening To You, They Are Happening Through You\nWhere Talent Meets Opportunity</string>
    <string name="pessimist_exercises">The Mindful Bus Ride\nCultivating Calm And Stress Tolerance\nDenied Facts And Feelings Are Still Facts And Feelings\nStrengthen Your Flexibility Muscle\nTaking Pride In Your Achievements\nThe Glass-Half-Full Mentality\nThe Real Consequences Of Problem Solving</string>
    <string name="doer_exercises">The Mindful Bus Ride\nBenefits Of Achieving Self-Actualization\nCultivating Calm And Stress Tolerance\nDrained Achiever To Proud Achiever\nPromote Spontaneity And Openness\nResist The Impulse To Act\nTaking Pride In Your Achievements</string>
    <string name="conformer_exercises">The Mindful Bus Ride\nEnd Indecisiveness And Neediness\nGiver, Taken, Or Sharer?\nLearn To Speak Assertively\nSetting Your Limits\nThings Are Not Happening To You, They Are Happening Through You\nWhy Self-Care Isn\'t Selfish</string>
    <string name="dreamer_exercises">The Mindful Bus Ride\nDenied Facts And Feelings Are Still Facts And Feelings\nDon\'t Ignore Your Emotions: Combat Alexithymia\nGrowth is Being Sugar-Coated\nStop Over-Identification\nThe Real Consequences Of Problem Solving\nYou Choose: Realistic Optimism vs. Toxic Positivism</string>
    <string name="info_tutorial">Tap on any of the items in the results list to get more info about it</string>
    <string name="url_to_website">https://emotions-at-work.activehosted.com/f/3</string>
    <string name="url_details">"For more details, please click this text to visit our website: "</string>
    <string name="onboarding">Ready to discover your predominant mental models?</string>


</resources>